Guide to the The Exit Art Archive 1982 - 2011 MSS 343
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
Exit Art Archive
Bulk, 1982-2010
1979-2011
MSS 343
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
65.0 linear feet
Founded in 1982 by Jeanette Ingberman and Papo Colo, Exit Art was an interdisciplinary cultural center in New York City that presented innovative exhibitions, films and performances that reflected a commitment to contemporary issues and ideas. The Exit Art Archive includes exhibition administrative files, artist research and records, events promotional and press materials, correspondence, ephemera, photographic elements, video, audio, and data storage components.
Colo, Papo
Ingberman, Jeanette
Arrangement
The first three series are available for research while the rest of the collection remains in process. This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Exhibition Files includes documentation of all aspects of creating and executing exhibitions, including research, artist profiles, correspondence, financial records, promotional and press materials. This series is arranged chronologically by exhibition opening date.
Series II: Jeanette Ingberman Files is arranged into three subseries that separate exhibition press pack materials, personal correspondence and ephemera, and Exit Art administrative components. These materials are arranged chronologically, then alphabetically by record type.
Subseries A: Jeanette Ingberman Exhibition Files
Subseries B: Jeanette Ingberman Personal Files
Subseries C: Jeanette Ingberman Administrative Files
Series III: Potential Exhibitions consists of unrealized exhibitions. Record types include research and artist profiles. This series is arranged alphabetically by project title.
Series IV: Artists Files [In Process]
Series V: Photographic Materials [In Process]
Series VI: Video [In Process]
Series VII: Audio [In Process]
Series VIII: Data Storage [In Process]
Historical Note
Founded by director Jeanette Ingberman and artist Papo Colo as an alternative art space in 1982, Exit Art was an interdisciplinary cultural center that presented innovative exhibitions, films and performances that reflected a commitment to contemporary issues and ideas. With a substantial reputation for curatorial innovation and depth of programming in diverse media, Exit Art was always changing.
During its first decade, Exit Art presented artists whose work challenged notions of race, ethnicity, gender, sexuality, and equality. It mounted a series of mid-career retrospectives which helped to bring wider public attention and critical acclaim to artists who are now firmly established, including Jimmie Durham, Willie Birch, Krzysztof Wodiczko, Tehching Hsieh, Martin Wong, Adrian Piper, David Wojnarowicz and David Hammons.
In its second decade, Exit Art identified a new generation of young, emerging artists with diverse backgrounds and organized a series of exhibitions, launching the careers of artists such as Shirin Neshat, Fred Tomaselli, Nicole Eisenman, Roxy Paine, Patty Chang, Julie Mehretu, Sue DeBeer, Rirkrit Tiravanija and Chakaia Booker. Fever (1992), the first exhibition in the series, was named one of the ten most important shows of the decade by Peter Plagens in Newsweek.
In its final decade, Exit Art became a leading voice in experimental art, producing exhibitions that illuminated the pressing issues of its time while supporting artists whose works reflected cultural transformations. By 2012, its 30th and final year, Exit Art had organized more than 200 exhibitions, events, festivals and programs featuring more than 2,500 artists.
Biographical information provided by the Exit Art website.
Conditions Governing Access
Series I, II and II are open to researchers. Appointments are necessary for the use of manuscript and archival collections. Other series have not been processed and are not available.
Scope and Content
The Exit Art Archive consists of records documenting all aspects of the exhibition process, from conception to execution, to reception. This collection includes administrative files, artist profiles and research, ephemera, financial documents, promotional and press materials, professional and personal correspondence, photographic elements, and project proposals, in addition to video, audio, and data storage components.
Provenance
The Exit Art Archives was donated to NYU's Fales Library and Special Collections in 2012.
Ahearn, Charlie; Alvarez, Candida; Baranik, Rudolph; Beckett, Samuel, 1906-1989; Beiser, Maya; Birch, Willie; Cheang, Shu Lea; Chernishov, Michael; Cohen, Elaine Lustig; Dalen, Anton van; Davidovich, Jaime, 1936-; Durham, Jimmie; Edgar, Hachivi; Ennadre, Touhami; Exit Art (Gallery: New York, N.Y.).; Fay, Ming; Fekner, John; Galindo, Regina Jose; Gitlin, Michael; Hammond, Jane; Hammond, Red; Hammons, David; Hsieh, Tehching; Huang, Arlan; Kariya, Hiroshi; Kearns, Jerry; Keeley, Shelagh; Lujan, Pedro; Meyer, Melissa; Miller, Nachume; Mock, Richard; Neustein, Joshua; O'Brien, Michael James; Palasanean Balassanian, Sonia; Paternosto, Cesar; Piper, Adrian, 1948-; Rand, Archie; Roch, Jacques; Rosin, Paul; Ruiz, Raul; Sanchez, Juan; Sanchez, Rafael; Scaritt, Alan; Slonem, Hunt; Stevens, May; Tuck, Norman; Vicuna, Cecilia; Von Rydingsvard, Ursula, 1942-; Wodiczko, Krzysztof; Wojnarowicz, David; Wong, Martin; Zedd, Nick; Administrative records.; Alternative spaces (Arts facilities); Art and society.; Art criticism.; Art galleries (institutions).; Art |v Exhibitions.; Artists |z New York (State) |z New York |v Exhibitions.; Artists' writings.; CD-Rs.; Compact discs.; Correspondence.; Exhibition catalogs.; Invitations.; Negatives (photographic); Performance art.; Photographs.; Politics in art.; Press kits.; Resumes (personnel records); Social problems in art.; Transparencies.; VHS (TM); Video art |z United States.; Women artists |v Exhibitions.; Women artists |z United States.
- Series I: Exhibition Files
  Scope and Content
  Series I: Exhibition Files includes documentation of all aspects of creating and executing exhibitions, including research, artist profiles, correspondence, financial records, promotional and press materials. This series is arranged chronologically by exhibition opening date.
  - Illegal America [1982.01]: Research Materials - Court Cases, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Illegal America [1982.01]: Research Materials - "Law, Ethics, and the Visual Arts", 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Illegal America [1982.01]: Research Materials - Media, 1955 - 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Illegal America [1982.01]: Research Materials - "Art and the Law in 20th Century America" Dissertation by J. Ingberman, [1975] (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Illegal America [1982.01]: Invitations, February 10, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Illegal America [1982.01]: Press Release, February 10, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Illegal America [1982.01]: Artist File - Acconci, Vito, January 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Illegal America [1982.01]: Artist File - Akasegawa, Gempei, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Illegal America [1982.01]: Artist File - Aragon, Louis, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Illegal America [1982.01]: Artist File - Fekner, John, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Illegal America [1982.01]: Artist File - Giorno, John, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Illegal America [1982.01]: Artist File - Halpern, John, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Illegal America [1982.01]: Artist File - Hoffman, Abbie, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Illegal America [1982.01]: Artist File - Matta Clark, Gordon, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Illegal America [1982.01]: Artist File - Moorman, Charlotte, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Illegal America [1982.01]: Artist File - People's Flag Show, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Illegal America [1982.01]: Press Clippings, March, May 1982; 2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Illegal America [1982.01]: Catalog Proof (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Illegal America [1982.01]: Catalog Order Form (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Octopus [1982.02]: Invitations, July 30, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Octopus [1982.02]: Press Release, August 31, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Octopus [1982.02]: Budget (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Octopus [1982.02]: Correspondence - Baraka, Amiri (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Octopus [1982.02]: Press Clippings (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Octopus [1982.02]: Miami Book Fair International, 1987 - 1988 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Octopus [1982.02]: Exhibition - "China", June 4, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Dirty Pictures [1982.03]: Invitations, December 4, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Dirty Pictures [1982.03]: Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Dirty Pictures [1982.03]: Curator's Text (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Dirty Pictures [1982.03]: Press Clippings, 1982 - 1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Dirty Pictures [1982.03]: Exhibition Travel, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Tehching Hsieh [1983.01]: Artist's Statement and Exhibition Proposal, September 1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Tehching Hsieh [1983.01]: Invitations, February 22, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Tehching Hsieh [1983.01]: Postcards (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Tehching Hsieh [1983.01]: Press Release (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Tehching Hsieh [1983.01]: Budget, 1983; 1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Tehching Hsieh [1983.01]: Correspondence, 1981 - 1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Tehching Hsieh [1983.01]: Exhibition Images [Photocopies], 1981 - 1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Tehching Hsieh [1983.01]: Catalogue Essay [Drafts and Final Copy], 1981 - 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Tehching Hsieh [1983.01]: "Interview of Tehching Hsieh" by Jeanette Ingberman & Papo Colo for ARTCOM, 1981 - 1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Tehching Hsieh [1983.01]: Press Clippings, 1982 - 1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Forbidden Films [1984.01]: Research Materials - Censorship (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Forbidden Films [1984.01]: Research Materials - Censorship and Art, 1955, 1966, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Forbidden Films [1984.01]: Research Materials - Censored Films, 1954, 1971, 1982, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Forbidden Films [1984.01]: Research Materials - Censored Books, 1981, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Forbidden Films [1984.01]: Grant Proposal, "Interpreting Censorship" (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Forbidden Films [1984.01]: Invitations (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Forbidden Films [1984.01]: New York Public Library, 1983 - 1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Forbidden Films [1984.01]: Press Releases (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Forbidden Films [1984.01]: Contracts (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Forbidden Films [1984.01]: Correspondence, 1982 - 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Forbidden Films [1984.01]: Screening Schedule (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Forbidden Films [1984.01]: Film Distributors / Price List (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Forbidden Films [1984.01]: Public Programs - Panel Discussions, September 11 - October 9, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Forbidden Films [1984.01]: Press Clippings (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Forbidden Films [1984.01]: Catalog Sales, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Fantastic Landscape [1984.02]: Research Materials, 1982, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Fantastic Landscape [1984.02]: Price List (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Fantastic Landscape [1984.02]: Invitations (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Fantastic Landscape [1984.02]: Press Release (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Fantastic Landscape [1984.02]: Artist Biographies (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Fantastic Landscape [1984.02]: Visitor List / Sign-In Log (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Melissa Meyer [1984.03]: Invitations (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Melissa Meyer [1984.03]: Press Release (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Melissa Meyer [1984.03]: Biographical Information (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Melissa Meyer [1984.03]: Loan Information (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Melissa Meyer [1984.03]: Price List (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Melissa Meyer [1984.03]: Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Melissa Meyer [1984.03]: Press Clippings (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Melissa Meyer [1984.03]: Catalog Distribution, 1984, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Miralda: Santa Comida / Holy Food [1984.04]: Project Proposals and Sketches (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Miralda: Santa Comida / Holy Food [1984.04]: Contracts (NYSCA, El Museo del Barrio), 1983 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Miralda: Santa Comida / Holy Food [1984.04]: Invitations (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Miralda: Santa Comida / Holy Food [1984.04]: Press Releases, 1984 - 1985 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Miralda: Santa Comida / Holy Food [1984.04]: Biographical Information (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Miralda: Santa Comida / Holy Food [1984.04]: Budget (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Miralda: Santa Comida / Holy Food [1984.04]: Correspondence, 1982, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Miralda: Santa Comida / Holy Food [1984.04]: Advertisements, 1984 - 1985 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Miralda: Santa Comida / Holy Food [1984.04]: Press Clippings, 1984 - 1985 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Miralda: Santa Comida / Holy Food [1984.04]: Exhibition Travel, March 14 - April 10, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - The Beauty Not the Beast [1985.01]: Invitations (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - The Beauty Not the Beast [1985.01]: Press Release (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - The Beauty Not the Beast [1985.01]: Biographical Information (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - The Beauty Not the Beast [1985.01]: Loan Information (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - The Beauty Not the Beast [1985.01]: Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - The Beauty Not the Beast [1985.01]: Price List (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - The Beauty Not the Beast [1985.01]: Interview with Gary Mayer (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - The Beauty Not the Beast [1985.01]: Press Clippings (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - John Fekner: Idioblast [1985.02]: Press Release (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - John Fekner: Idioblast [1985.02]: Biographical Information (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - John Fekner: Idioblast [1985.02]: Slide List (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - John Fekner: Idioblast [1985.02]: Loan Information, 1985 - 1986 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - John Fekner: Idioblast [1985.02]: Advertisement (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - John Fekner: Idioblast [1985.02]: Press Clippings, 1984 - 1985 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Pedro Lujan [1985.03]: Invitations (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Pedro Lujan [1985.03]: Press Release (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Pedro Lujan [1985.03]: Biographical Information (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Pedro Lujan [1985.03]: Loan Agreement (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Pedro Lujan [1985.03]: Exhibition Checklist and Map (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Pedro Lujan [1985.03]: Price List (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Pedro Lujan [1985.03]: Interview with Pedro Lujan (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Pedro Lujan [1985.03]: Advertisement (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Pedro Lujan [1985.03]: Press Clipping (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Ringside Gallery: Trine Bumiller [1985.04]: Price List (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Ringside Gallery: Trine Bumiller [1985.04]: Invitations, February 14, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Ringside Gallery: Trine Bumiller [1985.04]: Press Release, February 14, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Ringside Gallery: Trine Bumiller [1985.04]: Biographical Information (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Ringside Gallery: Trine Bumiller [1985.04]: Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Surplus Show [1985.05]: Invitations, March 28, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Surplus Show [1985.05]: Press Release, March 28, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Surplus Show [1985.05]: Correspondence to Phyllis Rosenzweig, April 2, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Surplus Show [1985.05]: Exhibition Zine (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Surplus Show [1985.05]: Price List (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Ringside Gallery: Michael Mulhern [1985.06]: Price List (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Ringside Gallery: Michael Mulhern [1985.06]: Invitations, March 28, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Ringside Gallery: Michael Mulhern [1985.06]: Biographical Information (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Oracle [1985.07]: Grant Information (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Oracle [1985.07]: Invitations to Artists (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Oracle [1985.07]: Artist Acceptance Letters (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Oracle [1985.07]: Artist Rejection Letters (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Oracle [1985.07]: Artist Lists (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Oracle [1985.07]: Invitations, April 28, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Oracle [1985.07]: Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Oracle [1985.07]: Budget (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Oracle [1985.07]: Rental Information (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Oracle [1985.07]: Video Information (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Michael Gitlin [1985.08]: Invitations, May 2, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Michael Gitlin [1985.08]: Biographical Information (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Michael Gitlin [1985.08]: Correspondence, 1984 - 1985 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Michael Gitlin [1985.08]: Loan Information (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Michael Gitlin [1985.08]: Price List (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Michael Gitlin [1985.08]: Catalog Requests (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Ringside Gallery: Arlan Huang [1985.09]: Invitations, May 2, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Ringside Gallery: Arlan Huang [1985.09]: Biographical Information (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Ringside Gallery: Arlan Huang [1985.09]: Loan Information (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Alan Scaritt [1985.10]: Invitations, June 6, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Alan Scaritt [1985.10]: Press Release, June 6, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Alan Scaritt [1985.10]: Biographical Information (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Alan Scaritt [1985.10]: Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Alan Scaritt [1985.10]: Mailing List (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Alan Scaritt [1985.10]: Loan Information, June 6, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Alan Scaritt [1985.10]: Price List (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Alan Scaritt [1985.10]: Floor Plan (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Alan Scaritt [1985.10]: Press Clipping - Robert Atkins for Arts, October 1985 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Norman Tuck [1985.11]: Invitations, June 6, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Norman Tuck [1985.11]: Biographical Information (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Norman Tuck [1985.11]: Loan Information, June 5, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Norman Tuck [1985.11]: Press Clippings (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Norman Tuck [1985.11]: Price List (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Norman Tuck [1985.11]: Kinetic Sculpture Video Catalog, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Jerry Kearns [1985.12]: Invitations, September 12, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Jerry Kearns [1985.12]: Press Release, September 12, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Jerry Kearns [1985.12]: Biographical Information (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Jerry Kearns [1985.12]: Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Jerry Kearns [1985.12]: Interviews with Kearns, 1985 - 1986 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Jerry Kearns [1985.12]: Price List (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Jerry Kearns [1985.12]: Loan Information, September 9, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Jerry Kearns [1985.12]: Sales, 1985, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Jerry Kearns [1985.12]: Painting List, September 1985 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Jerry Kearns [1985.12]: Press Clippings (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Jerry Kearns [1985.12]: Exhibition Travel - Modernism Gallery, San Francisco, April 11 - May 24, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Jerry Kearns [1985.12]: Photocopies of Prints (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Ringside Gallery: Jacques Roch [1985.13]: Invitations, September 12, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Ringside Gallery: Jacques Roch [1985.13]: Biographical Information, September 1, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Ringside Gallery: Jacques Roch [1985.13]: Loan Agreement, September 9, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Ringside Gallery: Jacques Roch [1985.13]: Price List (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Elaine Lustig Cohen [1985.14]: Invitations, October 17, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Elaine Lustig Cohen [1985.14]: Press Release (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Elaine Lustig Cohen [1985.14]: Grant Information (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Elaine Lustig Cohen [1985.14]: Biographical Information (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Elaine Lustig Cohen [1985.14]: Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Elaine Lustig Cohen [1985.14]: Price List (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Elaine Lustig Cohen [1985.14]: Loan Information, 1985 - 1986 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Elaine Lustig Cohen [1985.14]: List of Collectors (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Elaine Lustig Cohen [1985.14]: Press Clipping - Vivien Raynor for The New York Times, November 1, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Elaine Lustig Cohen [1985.14]: Catalog Invoice, October 16, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Ringside Gallery: Candida Alvarez [1985.15]: Invitations, October 17, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Ringside Gallery: Candida Alvarez [1985.15]: Biographical Information (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Ringside Gallery: Candida Alvarez [1985.15]: Price List (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Ringside Gallery: Candida Alvarez [1985.15]: Loan Information, 1985 - 1986 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Hunt Slonem [1985.16]: Price List (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Hunt Slonem [1985.16]: Invitations, November 27, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Hunt Slonem [1985.16]: Press Release, November 27, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Hunt Slonem [1985.16]: Biographical Information (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Hunt Slonem [1985.16]: Loan Information, 1985 - 1986 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Hunt Slonem [1985.16]: Mailing Lists (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Hunt Slonem [1985.16]: Press Clippings, 1985 - 1986 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Ringside Gallery: The Showroom [1985.17]: Loan Information, 1985 - 1986 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Ringside Gallery: The Showroom [1985.17]: Price List (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Richard Mock [1986.01]: Invitations, January 4, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Richard Mock [1986.01]: Press Release, January 4, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Richard Mock [1986.01]: Biographical Information (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Richard Mock [1986.01]: Correspondence, 1982 - 1983, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Richard Mock [1986.01]: Loan Information (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Richard Mock [1986.01]: Price Lists, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Richard Mock [1986.01]: Press Clippings (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Ringside Gallery: The Showroom [1986.02]: Loan Information (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Ringside Gallery: The Showroom [1986.02]: Price List (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Not About Abstraction [1986.03]: Invitations, February 6, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Not About Abstraction [1986.03]: Price List (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Not About Abstraction [1986.03]: Loan Information (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Media Hostages [1986.04]: Invitations, February 15, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Media Hostages [1986.04]: Press Release, February 15, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Media Hostages [1986.04]: Exhibition Program (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Media Hostages [1986.04]: Grant Information (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Media Hostages [1986.04]: Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Media Hostages [1986.04]: Press Clippings and Advertisements (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Consensus: Today's Art in an Overpopulated City [1986.05]: Invitations, March 8, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Consensus: Today's Art in an Overpopulated City [1986.05]: Artists' Resumes (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Consensus: Today's Art in an Overpopulated City [1986.05]: Price List (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - The Gallery Show [1986.06]: Invitations, April 3, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - The Gallery Show [1986.06]: Press Release, April 3, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - The Gallery Show [1986.06]: Exhibition Program (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - The Gallery Show [1986.06]: Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - The Gallery Show [1986.06]: Loan Information (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - The Gallery Show [1986.06]: Condition Reports - In (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - The Gallery Show [1986.06]: Condition Reports - Out (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - The Gallery Show [1986.06]: Price List (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - The Gallery Show [1986.06]: Guest List / Sign-In, April 3 - 26, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - The Gallery Show [1986.06]: Press Clippings (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Exit in 3 [1986.07]: Research Materials, 1985 - 1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Exit in 3 [1986.07]: Invitations, April 25, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Exit in 3 [1986.07]: Press Release, April 25, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Exit in 3 [1986.07]: Correspondence, 1985 - 1986 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Exit in 3 [1986.07]: Biographical Information - Papo Colo (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Exit in 3 [1986.07]: Advertisements (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Exit in 3 [1986.07]: Guest Lists, 1985 - 1986 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Exit in 3 [1986.07]: Film / Video Festival Submission Forms (Box 7, Folder 8)